Finding Aid for the Miscellaneous Manuscripts Collection LSC.0100
UCLA Library Special Collections
Miscellaneous manuscripts collection
circa 1750
UCLA Library Special Collections
LSC.0100
136.5 linear feet (261 boxes, 6 cartons, and 20 oversize boxes)
Conditions Governing Access
Portions of collection unprocessed. Material in the boxes 204-280 are unavailable for access. Please contact Special Collections reference (spec-coll@library.ucla.edu) for more information.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9942334393606533
Scope and Content
Collection consists of miscellaneous 18th, 19th, and 20th century manuscript materials, typewritten transcripts, holographs, and facsimiles. Includes literary manuscripts, correspondence, letters, diaries, scripts, legal documents, photographs, and audio tapes related to various prominent literary, political, and intellectual figures.
Online Items Available
Portions of this collection have been digitized and are available online: Miscellaneous Manuscripts Collection (4 items).
Manuscripts.; Letters.
- Author not Identified
  - [No Author Given]. First half of 13th century, from a Bible concordance., (2 leaves). (Box 178)
  - No Author Given. Ink and wash drawings., (23 items). (Box 186)
    Scope and Contents note
    Used to illustrate The Lily: A book for children. Published by John Harris in 1808 (Moon 671B).
    General note
    (Two of the illustrations have not been identified.)
  - No Author Given. Ink and wash drawings., (3 items). (Box 186)
    Used to illustrate The Two Boys; or, The Reward of Truth. Published by John Harris in 1808 (Moon 938).
  - 2 letters [holograph, in French], addressed to Cher Monseiur, and newspaper article (p. 2? 1932)., 1922 & 1931; (3 items, 3pp.). (Box 282, Folder 11)
    On Bibliotheque Communale et Musees of the Ville D'Abbeville letterhead.
  - ABC fnr das liebe Paar Bernet-Stehelin auf den 23. Feber. 1796. (German). 1796 29 cards. 12.5 x 8 cm. Manuscript. (Box 25)
    The borders of the cards are engraved. Each letter of the alphabet is represented by a sententious four-line poem advising the young couple how to be happily married. In a green paper slipcase.
  - Año de 1898. Padron numero 1, del Districto de Tulancingo., (Holograph, bound). (Box 192, Folder 18)
  - Bible. Manuscripts, Hebrew. O.T. Pentateuch. Torah made for practice. Hebrew. 14th century 1 item. 58 x 60 cm. Manuscript. (Box 23)
    Oversize. Not complete. This fragment is a practive sheet prepared in a school of Torah studies. Five columns of 51 lines each on brown leather. Mounted in a tan cloth portfolio.
  - Book list [holograph]., n.d.; (1 item). (Box 282, Folder 8)
    Incomplete, C - Z only.
    Front cover missing, lists author, title, size and publication date.
    From Ogden Collection (Collection 785).
  - Book of devotion., 17th Century(?); (1 item, 166pp. [holograph, in Spanish]). (Box 282, Folder 18)
    Entries re religious devotion and personal acts.
  - Booklet of poems., 1904 14 April; (1 item, 20pp. [typescript, bound]). (Box 284, Folder 12)
    19 poems for dinner to Miss Laura McKinstny, given by Mrs. Robert Oxnard.
    Purchase: Kay Caughren.
  - Bibliography of Pinnochio, newspaper articles and ephemera and display cards., (8 items, 68pp. [manuscript typescript]). (Box 289, Folder 9)
    List of books in English relating to, and foreign language Pinnochio versions.
    Gift of Russell Shank.
  - Brief history of the California league of women voters. Circa 1920 12 l. Typescript. (Box 6)
    Immediate Source of Acquisition note
    Gift: Bureau of Governmental Research.
    Possibly by Dora Haynes (Mrs. John R. Haynes).
  - Document of indenture., 1643 (Box 193, Folder 3)
    Agreement made between Thomas Budden of Bothomwood and Stephen Bowdyde of Wimborne, August 6, With signatures.
    SEE: card for Vellum.
  - Collection of prints, 10 engravings and photographs of American and English theatre stars., 19th Century; (10 items). (Box 288, Folder 8)
    Stars include: Jenny Lind, Joseph Jefferson, Kemble and Edmund Keen.
    [Also], Copies of Punch.
    Purchase: F. Craven.
  - Correspondence, 2 letters [holograph, in French] from Adolphe Schreyer and J.E. Saintiny (?)., n.d. & 1877; (2 items, 2pp.). (Box 282, Folder 12)
    Both re upcoming visits to Paris and Rome respectively. Letters possibly connected.
  - Family book? [in Spanish]., n.d.; (Holograph, bound on vellum). (Box 202, Folder 5)
    Bought by Larry Laurhass.
  - The George Altman Theatre Library., n.d.; (Bound). (Box 194, Folder 16)
    Details library's holdings.
    Gift of Patricia P. Altman.
  - Hair samples., n.d. (Box 194, Folder 8)
    Three locks sewn to paper, identified as "E.Owens," "Amanda" and "W.Owens."
    Gift of Fern B. Clapper, August 1955.
  - The Hungarian Revolution., n.d.; (2 items). (Box 286, Folder 11)
    On 2 cassettes, copies of a 4-record set.
  - La Casa no.5 Calle del Tercer Orden de S. Agustin [in Spanish]., 1682-1880; (Holograph, bound). (Box 203, Folder 1)
    Collection of notarized documents of ownership for a Mexico City dwelling.
  - Letter [holograph] to Dear Mama, from Your Darter [sic]., 1833(?) July; (1 item, 2pp.). (Box 288, Folder 6)
    re day at her uncle's home. Apparently from a child.
  - Letter of Indenture, between Thomas Carr and James Oswin for the sum of 5 shillings., 1754; (1 item, 1p.). (Box 193, Folder 7)
    Bears stamps and partial wax seal. On vellum.
    SEE: card for VELLUM.
  - Letters re Egyptian politics, economics and the Suez Canal (3 of 10)., 1871-1911; (5 items, 26pp.). (Box 285, Folder 3)
    Letters no.6-10.
    (See index, folder 1)
  - Letters re Egyptian politics, economics and the Suez Canal (4 of 10)., 1871-1911; (5 items, 19pp.). (Box 285, Folder 4)
    Letters no.11-15.
  - Letters re Egyptian politics, economics and the Suez Canal (5 of 10)., 1871-1911; (5 items, 30pp.). (Box 285, Folder 5)
    Letters no.16-20.
  - Letters re Egyptian politics, economics and the Suez Canal (6 of 10)., 1871-1911; (5 items, 21pp.). (Box 285, Folder 6)
    Letters no.20-25.
  - Letters re Egyptian politics, economics and the Suez Canal (7 of 10)., 1871-1911; (5 items, 16pp.). (Box 285, Folder 7)
    Letters no.26-30.
  - Letters re Egyptian politics, economics and the Suez Canal (8 of 10)., 1871-1911; (5 items, 20pp.). (Box 285, Folder 8)
    Letters no.31-35.
  - Letters re Egyptian politics, economics and the Suez Canal (9 of 10)., 1871-1911; (5 items, 18pp.). (Box 285, Folder 9)
    Letters no.36-40.
  - Letters re Egyptian politics, economics and the Suez Canal (10 of 10)., 1871-1911; (5 items, 29pp.). (Box 285, Folder 10)
    Letters no.41-45.
  - Letters re Egyptian politics, economics and the Suez Canal (1 of 10)., 1871-1911; (2 items, 16pp. [typescript, 2 copies]). (Box 285, Folder 1)
    Index.
  - Letters re Egyptian politics, economics and the Suez Canal (2 of 10)., 1871-1911; (5 items, 19pp.). (Box 285, Folder 2)
    Letters no.1-5.
  - McKinley notes on Dean Webster's Sir Walter Scott and Shakespeare courses (University of Edinburgh)., 1926; (3 items, approximately 450pp.). (Box 281, Folder 12)
    3 loose leaf notebooks bound with string.
  - Manuscript - 17th Century Pedagogue., n.d.; (1 item, 3pp. [holograph octavo]). (Box 282, Folder 17)
    Signed "P.J.," religious and moral instruction for children and 18 lines of notes, all in verse.
    Typescript copy included.
  - Manuscript fragments. Collection of fragments of early manuscripts. 7 items. Manuscript. (Box 23)
    Oversize. See also Box 70 for smaller items.
  - Manuscript - Unidentified Samaritan [in Hebrew]., n.d.; (1 item, 8pp. - Has several repairs). (Box 283, Folder 8)
    NOTE: Belonged to J.P. Barker, not part of Bible Collection.
  - Manuscripts, Latin. Documents., 14th Century. (Box 199, Folder 6)
    9 documents (photostat) and 1 photograph of document with seal, in Latin.
    From Gifts.
  - Marriage and birth record. (Pennsylvania Dutch?). 1822-1832 1 leaf. 37 x 27 cm. Watercolor drawing. (Box 23)
    Oversize. Record of birthdates and marriage of Leonard H. Humason and Mary Sykes Humason in a central heart. Smaller hearts and stylized flowers surround it. Four of the smaller hearts have been filled in with the birthdates of the Humason children. The name of the artist is indecipherable.
  - Memorandums of the road and the march of a corps of troops from Savannah to Augusta and some subsequent occurrences. 1779 January-April 28 p. manuscript. 23 cm. maps. (Box 32)
    The manuscript is from the Abertarff Collection belonging to T. F. Fraser of Abertarff. Aldine Purchase.
    Another copy: 1 reel 35 mm negative microfilm. An account of Sir Archibald Campbell's expedition against Augusta, Georgia with a British force sent from New York to Georgia by a member of his staff. The route of the Expedition is described in black ink with notes in red ink telling of military events at each stage of the march. Included are a folding watercolor map of the coast of Georgia and 6 pen and watercolor sectional maps of the route of the Expedition.
  - Memoria estadistica de Tulancingo. Año de 1862., (Holograph, bound). (Box 192, Folder 17)
  - Mining and land stock certificates for various Central American and Cuban companies. 36 pieces. (Box 16)
    Gift of Professor Roland D. Hussey, 1958 December.
    Certificates of the following companies: British Central American Land Co.; Royal Santiago Mining Co.; and Bolibar Mining Association.
  - [New Orleans, Battle of, 1815 - documents]. circa 1809-1816 5 pieces. (Box 16)
    Aldine Purchase.
    Includes: A letter from Brigadier General David Banister Morgan (1773-1848) to Major General Andrew Jackson, Camp Right Bank, [Louisiana], 1815 February 4. A letter from Col. Robert Nicholas (1793-1857) to Colonel Robert Butler, Cantonment Davis, [Louisiana?], 1816 March 8. Muster roll of field and staff officers of Major Nathaniel Powers [I], Battalion of Madison County mounted gunmen in the service of the United States on an expedition against the Creek Indians under the command of Major General Andrew Jackson [1809?]. An exchange note for Creek chief Spakakhafeo from Aide de Camp Thomas Langford Butler (1789-1880), 1814 September 20. A certification by Major Nathaniel Powers concerning provisions, 1814 January 29.
  - New York (City) Mayor. Passport of Charles C. Walden, New York. 1808 July 15 1 page. Printed form filled in and signed. (Box 9)
    Signed by DeWitt Clinton as Mayor of New York.
  - Palos verdes. Title Insurance and Trust. Printed magazine (advertisement?) on highlights of city., (1 item). (Box 193, Folder 8)
    Front and back cover in fragments - Very Brittle.
  - Sacramento letter. 2 als. 18-- (Box 5)
    Gift of Lindley Bynum 1947 Feb 20.
    (Ask him about this)
  - Short stories., n.d.; (6 typescripts, carbon). (Box 201, Folder 12)
    One signed Edith Klopfer, two untitled, with 22 loose photographs.
  - Stammbuch [German: album] (item 1 of 3)., 1810-1919; (1 item, 73 leaves). (Box 284, Folder 16)
    With holograph inscriptions [in German, 1 in Latin], 4 with etchings on back.
  - Stammbuch (?) [German: album] (item 2 of 3)., 1886-1887; (1 item, 45 leaves - Bound). (Box 284, Folder 16)
    Title page: Poesie [German: poetry], 29 entries [in German], most quotes from German authors.
  - Stock certificates. circa 1910-1930
    Miscellaneous blank stock certificates chiefly for southern California investment companies. 19 certificates.
  - Teacher's certificates, the state of Maine. 1873-1889 6 pieces in one folder. (Box 18)
    Recommendations for Martha (Mattie) L. Buzzell, later Cleaves. Form certificates of various townships in Maine, together with one holograph recommendation.
  - Teatro Hidalgo. 1934 February 5. (Box 29, Folder 46)
  - Theater Zeitung, nos. 116-117. 1922. (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Urning my living. An account of fifteen months experience written at sixteen and seventeen upon the suggestion of a friend. Circa 1935 4 p. l., 313 leaves. 28 x 21.5 cm. Typescript. (Box 28)
    A frank account of a male prostitute. Apparently unpublished.
  - Various (Box 282, Folder 2, 21)
    - 4 letters. Sample autograph card (John G. Whittier?)., 1858-1926.; (5 items, 6pp. [holograph]). (Box 282, Folder 2)
      Card unrelated to letters.
      Gift of Miss Nisbit (UCLA Department of English).
    - 4 letters., 1869-1879.; (6 items, 6pp. [holograph, one in French]). (Box 282, Folder 21)
      re donation of church window, a Bishop's cancellation of a visit, book hymnal rejection, unknown. Letters probably unrelated.
  - Western bookman. A quarterly. Volume 1, number 1 and 2. Portland Oregon, Glen Coffield. 1956- (Box 24)
    In: Coffield, Glen, Collection. Editor: 1956- Glen Coffield.
  - Whig Party. National Committee, Washington, D. C. Letters received. 1844 June - 1845 August 32 letters. (Box 32)
    Aldine purchase.
- Author Identified
  - A Beckett, Arthur William, 1844-1909. Correspondence. 1899 2 items. Holograph. (Box 36)
    1 letter to Eden Phillpotts, 1899 December 14.
  - A Beckett, Gilbert Abbott, 1811-1856. Correspondence. 1846 5 items. Holograph. (Box 36)
    1 letter to Edward Litt Laman Blanchard, 1846 March 22.
  - A Beckett, Gilbert Arthur, 1837-1891. Correspondence. 3 items. Holograph. (Box 36)
  - Abbeydale, Lord Allen. Letter to "Bill.", 1977 (Box 200, Folder 2)
    Dated July 29, 1977, re pending trip to USA, and debates in House of Lords.
  - Ackerley, Joe Randolph, 1896-1967. Letters to various persons. V.p., v.d. 1932 Nov 1 (Box 5)
    Removed from His, Hindoo Holiday1932: PR6001 / A182h.
  - Adams, Mrs. Annie (Brown) 1843-1926. Some pleasant recollections of Concord People. Petrolia, California. undated 13 leaves. 20.5 cm. Holograph. (Box 17)
    Mrs. Adams (a daughter of John Brown, the abolitionist) records her memories, and what others have told her, of Louisa May Alcott and her family, Nathaniel Hawthorne, and Lord Alfred Tennyson, in the period circa 1860. There is no reference to John Brown in the manuscript. Unpublished.
  - Adams, John Quincy, 1767-1848. To Josiah Quincy, Washington, D.C. 1829 May 20 (Box 11)
    Introducing Richard Henry Lee and a Mr. Fendall (possibly Philip Richard Fendall) visiting Harvard University because of interest in literature and science. 1 l. Holograph signed. In blue buckram portfolio with flaps.
  - Ainsworth, William Francis, 1807-1896. Correspondence. 1 piece.
    Heise purchase: cat. 195.
  - Ainsworth, W.H. 3 letters, to My Dear Moran (1840) and John Edward Taylor (1851 & 1856)., 1840-1856; (3 items, 4pp. [holograph]). (Box 283, Folder 7)
    Letters to Taylor re publishing work, rejections. Letter to Moran re dinner invitation.
    Purchased: Arundel.
  - Ainsworth, William Harrison, 1805-1882. Correspondence to various persons. v.p., v.d. 25 items. Holograph. (Box 8)
    Also includes original water color by P. H. Nicholson, 1843 and a small original water color by artist Tony Johannot (?). 1 letter, n.d., from Johannot with reference to Ainsworth. Includes 1 letter to Albert Richard Smith, 1850 April 30.
  - Alden, James, 1810-1877. Correspondence. 1 folder. (Box 25)
  - Aldington, Mrs. Hilda (Doolittle), 1886-1961. Correspondence to the Reverend Charles C. Bubb. v.p. 1916, 1917, and undated 12 items. Holograph. (Box 18)
    These letters relate to the publishing of Mrs. Aldington's poetry by the Reverend Bubb who operated the Clerk's Private Press in Cleveland, Ohio. Most of the letters are undated. See also: the letters of Richard Aldington to the Reverend Bubb, also in Box 18.
  - Aldington, Richard, 1892-1962. Correspondence with Lawrence Clark Powell, v.p. 1944-1962 101 pieces, in 2 folders. (Box 18)
    Correspondence deals with personal and literary matters. Frequent mention is made of Kershaw's bibliography of Aldington's work. Dr. Powell's letters are carbon copies of the originals.
  - Aldington, Richard, 1892-1962. The eaten heart. n.p. circa 1929 1 p.l., 9 leaves. 26 cm. Typescript (carbon). (Box 18)
    "Typescript from which was hand-set by Nancy Cunard the poem of the Eaten Heart ... for the Hours Press edition of 200 numbered and signed copies, at Chapelle-Reanville, Normandy, France, spring, 1929." With this: an unbound copy of the Hours Press edition of The Eaten Heart, signed by Aldington.
  - Aldington, Richard, 1892-1962. Correspondence to Herman A. Rappaport. Montpellier, France. 1953-1958 11 items. Typescript, signed. (Box 18)
    The last two letters are written from Sury en Vaux, Cher. Mr. Rappaport lived in Westport, Connecticut, and in 1954 moved to Brooklyn, New York.
  - Aldington, Richard, 1892-1962. Letters to the Reverend Charles C. Bubb. v.p. 1916-1919 18 items. Holograph. (Box 18)
    These letters related to the publishing of some of Aldington's poetry by the Reverend Bubb who operated the Clerk's Private Press in Cleveland, Ohio. Enclosed with the letter of 1918 January 21, is a letter (1918 January 15) from Jean de Gourmont to Aldington, giving permission for Bubb to publish some of the work of his brother, Remy de Gourmont.
  - Aldington, Richard, 1892-1962. Correspondence to Mr. Garth Cate. 1935 June 12 1 item. Typescript. (Box 18)
    Another copy (of many different letters). 1 reel 35 mm negative microfilm. 1 letter (Xerox copy) to Mr. Garth Cate.
  - Aldington, Richard, 1892-1962. [Movietones. n.p.] 1932 7 sheets. 62 X 19 cm. Galleys with the holograph alterations. (Box 18)
    "Movietones" was limited to 10 copies, privately printed. These proofs contain some deleted material. With a holograph inscription, signed, on the first leaf. In a grey linen case with a morocco backstrip.
  - Alexander, Samuel, 1859-1938. Correspondence, holograph signed, to Dr. A. Wolff. 1921 September 28 1 p. (Box 25)
    Removed from a book in the Spinoza collection.
  - Alford, Henry, 1810-1871. Correspondence. 2 items. Holograph. (Box 17)
  - Allcott, Simeon P. Correspondence. 1833 December 28 1 page. A.L.S. (Box 9)
    To Henry O'Reilly, Rochester [New York]. Also signed by George W. Pratt. Letter forwarding the application for an act to incorporate the Mechanics Bank of Rochester.
  - Allen, Charles Richard. A notable biography. Miss Mantz and Mr. Murry on Katherine Mansfield. [n.p. (New Zealand)]. Ca. 1934 2 l. 26 cm. Typescript (carbon). (Box 4)
    A book review, published in "N.Z. Magazine, Jan.-Feb., 1934"
  - Allen, S. and M., To G. De Waln, Philadelphia. 1821 February 27 1 p. Holograph signed. (Box 15)
  - Ames, Limited. Ledger., 1917-1920 (Box 195, Folder 1)
    Listing stock transactions and management personnel.
  - Andrews, John, 1746-1813. Bill to E. Dutilh, Philadelphia. 1789 May 24 1 l. manuscript signed. (Box 25)
    Bill for board and tuition of Anthony Raybaud at the Episcopal Academy, Philadelphia. Signed by Andrews for receipt of payment.
  - Anthony, Henry Bowen, 1815-1884. Letter, Washington to H. H. Tilling? 1866 March 13 1 page. 21 cm. Holograph signed. (Box 10)
  - Antonio, Signor Il Diavolo. Playbills. Circa 1820-1850 (Box 23)
    Oversize. Seventeen of the eighteen playbills are printed on silk. See also Papers in box 126. 18 items. Printed.
  - Archer, Stevenson, 1786-1848. To the Editor of the Presbyterian [Philadelphia] Annapolis. 1835 December 9 1 page. A.L.S. (Box 9)
  - 1 letter to "Dear Mr. Douglas" Armistead, Walker Keith. 1 als. 1820 Oct 6 (Box 5)
    Removed from: HT Armistead, 1581 A tribute to the negro. A73t
  - Armer, Laura (Adams), 1874-1963. Correspondence to Laura Adams Armer. (Box 29)
    2 Holograph letters from Heinrick Willem van Loon. 1 typescript copy of letter from Austin Lewis; clippings. 1 folder.
  - Arnold, Thomas, 1795-1842. Correspondence to Mr. Ricahrd Conington, Esq., Boston, Lincolnshire, written from Fox How. 1838 July 13 1 p. Holograph signed. (Box 29)
    Heise purchase: cat. 244. 1952 April 24.
    Arnold, 19th century English author and then headmaster of Rugby, writes in answer to an inquiry from a father as to tuition, et cetera, at Rugby School.
  - Astor Family. Correspondence and documents, 1792-1930. 7 pieces. (Box 30)
    Includes shipping and stock accounts of John Jacob Astor. A letter from the same concerning North West Co. in the fur trade. A letter from WIlliam B., his son, to Thomas M. Olcott, 1860 November 26. And notes from Helen Astor, wife of Vincent Astor.
  - Atherton, Gertrude Franklin (Horn), 1857-1948. Correspondence. 3 items. Holograph. (Box 25)
    1 letter to Herman Whitaker, undated.
  - Atwater, John. 3 als to his mother. San Francisco. 1849. (Box 2)
    Gift of Leonard Atwater Smith.
    Also contains Hannah Boulton Camp's spectacles and an Inventory of effects of Samuel Boulton.
  - Austin, Mary (Hunter), 1868-1934. Note to May Sinclair., 1921 May; (1 item, 1p. [holograph, signed]). (Box 288, Folder 10)
    Quote from Lincoln: "That these dead shall not have died in vain."
    Card under Austin, Mary (Hunter).
  - Austin, Sarah (Taylor), 1793-1867. Letters to various persons. V.p., v.d. 6 items. Holograph. (Box 3)
    2 letters to Lady Charlotte Murchison, undated.
  - Aytoun, William Edmondstoune, 1813-1865. Correspondence. 3 items. Holograph. (Box 17)
  - Babcock, Dwight Vincent, 1909-. Correspondence from various persons to Dwight Babcock. 1934-1942 12 items. Typescript, signed. (Box 36)
    Gift of Dwight V. Babcock, 1961 January.
    Includes letters from Joseph T. Shaw, editor of "Black Mask;" Raymond Chandler; and Horace McCoy.
  - Badger, Admiral Charles J. Letter to Dudley A. Denison., 1914 (Box 200, Folder 3)
    (Commander in Chief, U.S. Atlantic Fleet) dated July 1914.
  - Baerwald, Hans H.
    - Papers., 1965-1971; (Approximately 50pp.). (Box 283, Folder 10)
      Correspondence and memoranda re articles, lectures, faculty, etc.
    - Papers., 1965-1971; (12 items, approximately 50pp. [typescripts]). (Box 283, Folder 11)
      Manuscripts [published].
    - Papers., 1965-1971; (19 items, approximately 30pp.). (Box 283, Folder 12)
      Articles [some in Japanese], lecture announcements, miscellaneous material.
  - Baillie, Joanna, 1762-1851. Letters to various persons. V.p., v.d. 2 items. Holograph. (Box 3)
  - Baldwin, Henry, 1780-1844. To Thomas Ellicott, Washington. 1832 January 22 1 page A.L.S. (Box 9)
  - Baldwin, Robert (Box 201, Box 202)
    - House addition., 1962 (Box 201, Folder 13)
      Plans and drawings by Richard Neutra.
      1 of 4.
    - Documents., 1962 (Box 202, Folder 1)
      Insurance matters re Richard Neutra addition.
      2 of 4.
    - Correspondence with Richard Neutra., 1962 (Box 202, Folder 2)
      3 of 4.
    - Miscellaneous., 1962 (Box 202, Folder 3)
      Reciepts, permits, letters, photos, one magazine and one newspaper article on Neutra.
      4 of 4.
  - Bancroft, Hubert Howe, 1832-1918. Correspondence. 1862-1889 4 pieces. Positive photostats. (Box 18)
    Letter from Brigham Young giving topographical information concerning Utah Territory,1862 April 28. Letter from Leland Stanford declining Bancroft's offer to print the Central Pacific Railroad Co.'s timetables in his "Guide," 1873 November 24. A Letter to H. L. Preston from the History Co. relating to financial arrangements for purchase of Bancroft's histories, 1889 January 21. Originals in the Bancroft LIbrary, University of California, Berkeley.
  - Banton, William T. Correspondence. 1803 March 8. 1 l. A.L.S. (Box 8)
    Purchased from Zeitlin, 1951 September 17.
    To Reuben Merrell, Lexington [?].
  - Barber, Noyes, 1781-1845. To H[esekiah] Niles, Washington. 1832 December 31 1 page. A.L.S. (Box 9)
  - Barclay, John M. To Robert D. Percy, Philadelphia. 1934 Oct 6 Holograph signed. (Box 4)
  - Barnard D[aniel] D[ewey] 1797-1861. Correspondence. 1836-1853. 8 A.L.S. (Box 9)
    Includes receipt dated: May 24, 1828.
  - Barnard, Grace. Correspondence. V.P. 1893-1931 8 items. Manuscript. (Box 2)